I need…
I need somewhere…
A secluded spot…
Somewhere out of sight…
Well, I'll get going then.
What is it?
Is something the matter, Simon?
Chloe, someone's there.
I don't want any trouble.
I'll leave right away.
I'm terribly sorry.
So…
Should I report her or something?
I suppose.
What now?
I'm scared… She's creeping me out.
-Chloe.
-Emma.
-Chloe et Emma.
TEN DAYS LATER
Welcome to Shingetsu Nathan's
Hall of Divination.
HALL OF DIVINATION
READ YOUR FORTUNE
Soar, dragon!
SOAR, DRAGON!
CONSULTING THE STARS…
TODAY'S FORTUNE - THINGS WILL
GO DOWNHILL BE PROACTIVE
I'm sorry.
I'm the one who owes you an apology.
I was zoned out.
PUBLIC EMPLOYMENT SERVICE CENTER
Say…
Isn't this fried piroshki
the new item from the convenience store?
I've been wanting to try one.
Is it new?
It costs less than 200 yen, right?
Wait, 150 yen? Really, and it's this big?
Yes, that's about how much it cost.
And it's piroshki,
so it's stuffed with juicy, meaty filling.
It's fried, meaning it's high in calories
and will power you through the entire day.
It's just the food
for someone seeking employment.
I'll buy the same thing for lunch.
Say…
Would you like to join me for lunch?
I was just thinking
about eating at a park nearby.
A park? I'm sold.
Delicious.
To tell you the truth, I bought it
because I thought it was curry bread.
What? That's not remotely the same thing.
Are you okay?
Right, it's an entirely different food.
Recently…
I started to let go of the small things.
I simply don't care anymore.
I can relate.
That's how I felt when I lost my job.
Is it a common thing to feel?
I'm Emma.
And I'm Konagaya.
Brown. That's my lucky color.
Lucky color? What's that, fortune-telling?
Yes. I recently met a fortune teller,
and she read my fortune.
I've been into fortune-telling lately too.
That might be another thing
we unemployed folks have in common.
Like Shingetsu Nathan.
That's who I was watching
when we bumped shoulders.
He used to be all over TV.
His catchphrase "Soar, dragon!"
was really popular at school.
I came across a fortune teller
by pure luck.
And I didn't plan for her
to read my fortune or anything.
Honestly, I didn't expect
her predictions to come true.
But they did. I was surprised.
Really now.
What sort of predictions were they?
Well… Can I get into it?
Sure.
That night, I was looking
for somewhere to sleep on the streets.
I found someone's porch
that seemed secluded,
and I laid down,
thinking I found a perfect spot.
I had reached my limit. I was dead tired.
That's when the resident found me.
Needless to say, she was shocked.
I don't want any trouble.
I'll leave right away.
I'm terribly sorry.
In a panic, I apologized and took off,
but then, my stomach
started to hurt out of the blue.
What now?
I'm scared… She's creeping me out.
I'm sorry to impose, but…
could I please use your restroom?
It would be such a big help.
-What?
Thank you very much. You saved me.
You'll freeze sleeping outside like that.
Right.
I poured some warm tea.
Would you like a cup?
Could I?
Thank you so much.
Please enjoy these cookies too.
You made my day.
Thank you.
Scrumptious.
I baked them myself.
Those are the leftovers.
Sorry there aren't many.
I used whole wheat flour.
It's crunchy, isn't it?
Yes, it's sure to keep me full. I love it.
That's what makes you happy?
It's tasty too.
To start, why is a young woman like you
trying to sleeping outside?
To tell you the truth,
I've been staying at Internet cafés.
But I'm running out of money
and the prices go up on weekends.
I was desperately trying to pinch pennies.
Wait, what?
Are you a runaway?
Or do you not have a home?
No. I was living with my ex,
but he's getting married.
His fiancée is expecting.
Sheesh.
I used to live with my mother,
but when I was 27,
she got sick and passed away.
My ex-boyfriend, whom I was working with,
asked if I wanted to move in with him.
Wait, do you guys still work together?
Well, the company went bankrupt.
Apparently, the girl he got pregnant
lined up another job for him.
Not only that, her parents are helping
with the down payment on a house.
That's the realistic option, I guess.
I went to the unemployment center,
but I can't register an address
since I don't have a permanent place.
So my job hunt hit a wall.
You're cooked.
Indeed I am.
If you lived with your ex for a long time,
can't you sue him and the woman
for compensation?
I don't want to take it that far…
He helped me
in my time of need, after all.
Did your ex pay all the rent
and living expenses?
No, we split them evenly.
Then you guys were on equal ground.
Not in the slightest.
If I made him mad,
he could have kicked me out.
You were walking on eggshells around him,
but in the end, you still got kicked out.
What am I supposed to do now?
All I do is look up fortune reading
on the internet.
It's the only thing
that gives me hope at this stage.
Chloe, why don't you read her fortune?
What?
Are you a fortune teller?
It's nothing that impressive.
It's just a hobby of mine.
It's more than a mere hobby.
Then please.
I don't care if it's inaccurate.
I just need hope.
Fortune-telling can accurately predict
your past and present.
These things are set in stone.
But reading the future
is a different story.
Why, you ask? Why do you think that is?
Well…
Your actions determine your future.
The future isn't set in stone.
If that's okay with you,
then I'll read your fortune.
What is this room?
My mediation room.
Isn't it relaxing in here?
Here.
Please write down your name and birthday.
Yes.
SHO EMMA
JUNE 15TH, 1995
Emma… Yoi?
It's Sho Emma.
"Sho Emma?"
Don't call me that.
It sounds like "shame."
You're 30 years old.
We're around the same age.
Mind taking a few steps back?
Oh,
mon…
Dieu!
She said I'd get caught up
in some incident in the near future.
An incident?
An incident with a fire.
Apparently, something to do with fire.
But she said this incident would steer me
in the right direction.
It doesn't make any sense, does it?
Not really.
I then had to pay her
the consultation fee, 1,000 yen.
What?
That was a big 1,000 yen for me.
But she allowed me to spend a night.
Only for tonight, you hear me?
Could I really?
This guest house
is equipped with a shower.
Please wash up before you get in the bed.
Yes.
I'm going back to the main house.
Are you set up? Any other questions?
No. Thank you so much.
I'm happy for you.
Yes, you guys saved me.
Remember,
you're only staying one night, Sho Emma.
I understand.
Sho Emma?
"Emma" is my surname,
and "Sho" is my name.
Thank you,
for everything from the cookies to tea,
then the restroom
and a night under your roof.
We live in a dangerous world.
Remember when an unhoused woman
was murdered at a bus stop?
And recently,
a woman was murdered in Okutama.
The last I heard,
the killer is still on the run.
Simon, thank you for cleaning up.
Sorry to keep you till late.
It's fine. Well, I must get going.
I'll come again next week.
Good night, Chloe, Emma.
Have a wonderful night.
Is Simon originally from overseas?
No. "Simon" is his surname.
His full name is Kenshiro Simon.
Surname, huh.
Also, I'm Kana Chloe.
Kana meaning "god's name."
I'm the owner of this house. I'm 32.
I'm two years older than you, Sho Emma.
It makes me a little uncomfortable
when you call me by my full name.
Really now.
Then…
Miss Emma.
Miss Emma?
I don't keep any valuables in here,
but please don't take necessities
like toilet paper with you.
I've got your full name and your birthday,
and I can call
the unemployment center for more info.
You've been a huge help.
I wouldn't steal from you.
The bed and the restroom are upstairs.
Good night.
She…
rubs me the wrong way, a little.
What do I even do starting tomorrow?
Hello, Miss Emma!
You awake?
I'm up.
Is something wrong?
Did you leave something behind?
So I did a little research.
What if you go to the welfare office
and apply for government assistance?
It says here,
you can use the welfare office
as your address if you don't have one.
Have a look.
I thought you're ineligible to receive aid
if you're fit to work.
If you're struggling,
being healthy doesn't disqualify you.
You pay your taxes.
You'd have a better luck of landing a job
if you apply for rent relief
and have a place of your own.
Look, you were about to sleep
on the streets.
You have every right to receive aid.
I know a real estate agent.
They can help you find a rental.
Here. A guide on how
to successfully apply for aid
and a referral for the real estate agent.
HOW TO SUCCESSFULLY
APPLY FOR AID - REFERRAL
What is it?
You're so generous,
I thought you were heaven-sent.
You paid for consultation.
Also, without a place to live,
you might be tempted
to sleep on my property again.
And that, I cannot have.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Her tone though…
Still, she's got a heart of gold.
She might be unfriendly, but she's better
than a friendly person who betrays me.
What is that?
Fire?
It's just a dream.
No way. That can't be right!
Chloe!
It's unlocked.
Chloe?
What a mansion!
Chloe!
Chloe?
Hold on…
Chloe!
Miss Emma?
Glad you're okay. There's a fire.
What's this stench? It smells.
Do you have a fire extinguisher?
I don't know.
At any rate, we need to call
the fire department.
That's…
I have to change before they arrive.
I'm gonna get changed.
Miss Emma, you call them.
Hold on, I left my phone behind!
In that case…
There's the home phone
by the entrance. Use that.
Goodness…
There's a fire.
A fire.
My address?
Chloe? Someone who lives here
should be calling…
Give me a sec.
Please stand by.
We're in Mitaka, I think.
It's the fancy, big house in Mitaka.
The fire was from a battery of a laptop
that hasn't been charged in ages.
It then spread to the linseed oil in the
wall cabinet of the kitchen downstairs.
Is this the fire predicted
by the fortune reading earlier?
The main house was burned,
but not completely.
She said she can stay
at the same guesthouse I was at
while the main house underwent repairs,
so she can resume her life.
And how did this incident
bring you fortune?
She said I can stay
at the guesthouse with her.
To repay me
for alerting her about the fire.
What a miracle.
But I still have to move out when
I save enough to rent my own place.
At the latest, she wants me gone
by the time the repairs are complete.
That's why I'm job hunting like this, but…
All her predictions came true.
What a shame it's just a hobby for her.
That's what I thought too,
so I suggested
she open a fortune-telling business.
To my surprise, she wholeheartedly agreed.
But she wants to do it hobby-level.
Keep it small.
So she's only opening shop one day a week.
I bet it'll become popular
in no time by word of mouth.
I'm not sure.
She charges 3,000 yen per session.
Also, Chloe isn't…
What do you call it? Friendly.
I gathered that from your story.
She really isn't.
She makes biting remarks.
She can learn to soften her tone.
I know I shouldn't complain
considering her generosity,
but it's like, our standard of living
couldn't be any more different.
Standard of living?
Yeah.
I told her I'd like to do the chores
since I'm boarding rent-free,
and then I made packaged ramen for lunch.
But she was like,
"You can't call this cooking."
Then, for dinner,
she said she wanted something with rice.
But listen to this.
She doesn't even own a rice cooker.
I see… Like, she prefers
to use a pressure cooker or a clay pot?
Yes! Exactly.
Rice sure is tasty
when it's cooked that way.
But how do you keep it warm
without a rice cooker?
I mean, that's true, but…
I worked a normal full-time job,
so I never knew
people had these preferences.
Though I've never used a clay pot
to cook rice,
I gave it my best shot to make her happy.
I can't stand it anymore.
This rice is burned and hard as rock.
Sorry.
You also made ramen
with half-cooked eggs mixed in the soup.
If I overcook it, the noodles get soggy.
So the eggs have to be undercooked.
Then make marinated eggs beforehand.
I've seen those at the store.
I'll buy them next time.
What? Just make them.
Wouldn't it be faster to buy them?
Miss Emma, you must be the type
to buy packaged shredded cabbage.
Yes.
I know it's more expensive that way,
but I can't eat the whole cabbage.
It's more convenient to use pre-cut
vegetables, and I can finish it.
You lived with your boyfriend, right?
Neither of you cooked?
We both worked overtime.
We were wiped by the end of day.
So we'd grab discounted sides
from the deli on the way home.
It's like…
What is it?
Nothing.
You've got your own approach to life.
Have you heard?
There's a new type of malnutrition
where you consume sufficient calories,
but you're missing certain nutrients.
Did you know? Chicken breast
and broccoli cover all bases.
What are you, a bodybuilder?
Of course not.
I don't drink protein shakes.
I thought so.
We were brought up differently.
No wonder our standard
of living is different.
What is it?
You've taken me under your wing.
I'd like to be helpful to you.
Well…
If anything comes up,
I'll ask for your help.
I'm gonna take a shower.
I hate drying my hair.
What? What is it?
Your hair… I can dry it for you.
How is it?
This is quite nice.
Really?
I hate drying long hair.
It takes forever and my arms get tired.
Can I be in charge
of blow-drying your hair?
I see.
It's like shredded cabbage.
You pay for the convenience
of not having to do it yourself.
Now I see.
Let me finish up.
I end up helping out with meals anyway,
as well as the laundry and cleaning.
You know what, though?
Chloe sounds like a kind person.
I suppose.
I won't deny that.
But she lacks friendliness
to the point I overlook her kindness,
or she's flat-out rude.
She openly said
your actions determine your future.
She sounds like
an honest fortune teller to me.
I'm still bothered somewhat.
Say…
Could I come in for a reading with her?
That's the gist of it.
I brought a guest for you.
Nice to meet you.
-Emma.
-Yes?
I told you I see clients
only once a week, on Sundays.
You're right.
I'm so sorry. I totally forgot.
It's fine. I came on a whim anyway.
It's not like fortune-telling
can give me the answer I'm looking for.
I'll go get ready.
Will you give me a second?
Emma, please show her
to the divination room.
Will do.
Thank you so much!
Shall we?
Thank you for waiting.
What a fit, Chloe.
You look like
you stepped out of a magazine.
Please step out
if you're not being seen today.
We need privacy.
Okay.
Well, enjoy.
Well then, please write down your name
and its pronunciation, your birthday,
and your current address.
Yes.
YUKIKO KONAGAYA
MITAKA - DECEMBER 3RD, 1986
Yukiko Konagaya.
What shall I read for you today?
Well, I…
I have a husband and a child.
I married a high earner
and moved into a high-rise apartment.
My child attends a private school.
And yet, I can't escape
the wealth disparity
that surrounds my daily life.
-The wealth disparity?
-Yes.
I obsess over the brand
of clothes and bags I own.
On social media too.
I play up my extravagant lifestyle
for everyone to see.
I desperately try
to keep up with the lifestyle
of those in my social circle.
But then…
Once, I was in the elevator with my child,
and they judged
the people who live below us.
Also, I was horrified
when my husband casually commented
on the type of car
parked by the apartment entrance.
At the same time,
when my husband's parents chatter
boisterously at a high-end restaurant,
I find myself judging them.
I'm repulsed by my own family members,
who look down on others,
but I'm no better than them.
Being with my family tires me out.
But I don't want to be alone.
What am I supposed to do?
As if you can tell me.
Shall we ask the cards?
Are they tarot cards?
No. Chronicle cards.
Chronicle cards?
They're for reading
the flow of time, I suppose.
There are twelve cards
from January to December,
seven cards from Monday to Friday,
and one additional card,
totaling 20 cards.
Each card represents a different concept,
and their meaning changes
depending on their position.
Fascinating…
I will now read your fortune
by randomly selecting five cards.
Oh,
mon…
Dieu!
The first card.
It represents your current situation.
February, upright. Card of Solitude.
Though you adorn yourself, you are lonely.
Your relationships are platonic.
In your mind, you love your family.
The second card.
It represents something from
the past that continues to affect you.
May, upright.
Card of Tradition.
It represents traditional values,
or an enclosed space.
It could also…
signify a patriarchal system.
The third card. The inner self.
Monday, upright. Card of Hesitation.
There's a hesitation.
It's the kind that comes with a secret.
For example, a love triangle,
or marriage…
Could it be romantic?
It's upright,
meaning the situation isn't messy.
Well…
if you don't want to talk about it,
I won't pry.
But does it ring a bell?
Yes it does.
The fourth card. The outer world.
Thursday, reversed. Card of Greed.
It seems you've grown weary
of lavishness and intimate relationships.
The final card.
It represents an event in the near future.
January, upright. Card of Encounter.
A good encounter awaits you.
A meeting with new beginnings.
And…
I see a park,
or a game.
Your lucky color is yellow.
My lucky color?
It's nothing.
A good encounter, then?
That's correct.
What was the reading about?
What was it about?
She wanted to know about her family.
Her family?
Does she have a family?
Why do you ask?
Oh, I was just wondering.
I ran into her at the unemployment center,
but I don't know anything else.
Say what? The unemployment center?
Yes.
You met an affluent married woman
at the unemployment center?
Affluent?
Also, I can't shake this feeling
that I've seen her before.
Now I'm curious.
This is it. Found it.
Huh? Found what?
She's a lifestyle influencer.
Yukiko Kamii, AKA "Camille."
I must've recognized her
from an online interview or something.
Take a look at this.
Camille herself had stopped
uploading new content six months ago.
CAMILLEKIKO
But I found a mutual mom friend,
then I dug into her network.
Chloe?
Apparently, her husband
declared bankruptcy,
and she's separated from her family.
"Konagaya" must be her former surname.
You found all that within hours.
You're a detective!
But why did she want to know
her past self's fortune?
She paid 3,000 yen for that?
Usually, people refrain from lying
during a reading.
You see, lying can alter the outcome.
I see.
While she must've had genuine concerns,
if her family's torn apart,
then her issues should be resolved.
Maybe she wanted to know
what she could've done differently
to change her fate.
Who knows what goes on in people's heads?
Fortune-telling can only reveal
your present
and provide a path forward.
Shall I pour something warm to drink?
Thank you.
CAMILLEKIKO
Off we go to a fusion Japanese restaurant!
We might've walked too far.
Have we? Then let's turn around.
Sorry…
No, I put you in charge of the directions.
It's nothing compared to
your generous offer to pay for lunch.
I can't wait
to try the fusion Japanese food.
Will you memorize the flavor
and recreate the recipe?
What? I can't do that.
Would you like one?
Oh, what?
It is you.
There's something I want to ask, Konagaya.
Sorry. As you can see, I'm on the clock.
-Emma.
-Yes.
Help her pass out the tissues.
Say what?
I'm counting on you.
I'll see you at Paris.
Bring her when you're done.
What about the fusion Japanese cuisine?
Paris?
Sorry to bother you so suddenly.
Paris is the name of a traditional café.
What business
does that fortune teller have with me?
She wants to get to the bottom
of a mystery.
A mystery?
Something about a person named Camille.
TRADITIONAL CAFÉ PARIS
Welcome in.
Sorry to impose.
-It's quite all right.
-Have you eaten yet?
This café's famous for a dish.
Would you like to try it?
My treat.
What?
Enjoy.
Egg sandwich. It's very delicious.
Thank you very much.
One for you too, Emma.
-Can I have one?
-Of course.
Thank you so much.
This is Simon.
When I collapsed by Chloe's front porch,
he gave me whole wheat cookies.
Come again?
The cookies that can power you
through the day.
What exactly are you talking about, Emma?
Simon runs this café,
despite being so young.
It was passed down to me though.
Please, enjoy.
-Thank you for the food.
-Thank you.
It's fantastic.
Why did you want to know the fortune
of your past self?
When Chloe slipped into
that gorgeous dress, it hit me.
Were you reminded
of when you were Camille?
Indeed.
I used to live that way too.
Then, I felt ashamed of who I'd become.
That's why I pretended to be my old self.
I've separated from my husband,
and I no longer live with my child.
I live alone in an apartment.
I thought I was finally set free,
that I don't have to perform anymore.
You should've asked
for the fortune of your current self.
Why throw away 3,000 yen like that?
My question would have been
the same regardless.
What?
What am I supposed to do?
I keep asking myself
the same old question.
Emma, that's the very question you had
when I read your fortune.
Huh?
Did I?
Maybe that's everyone's question
when they want to know their fortune.
"What am I supposed to do?"
It's a common thread among
us unemployed folks.
Sorry to intrude.
Chocolate banana crunch parfait.
That looks delectable!
Here.
If you'd like.
It's off the menu.
I had Simon make it just for us.
It uses homemade nougat chocolate crunch.
The pieces of pie crust and cookies
give it a nice crunch.
-Homemade?
-Yes.
Simon's hobby is parfait-making.
Hobby, huh?
-Hence it's off the menu.
-Yes.
Simon visits Chloe's place
every week to make parfaits.
That's why he was there
when she read my fortune.
The whole wheat cookies you had
were leftovers from a parfait.
That's something else.
I've heard of sushi masters visiting
the wealthy to make sushi, but…
-Thank you.
-Bon appétit.
Time to dig in.
This is delicious.
Hey, Konayuki!
Konayuki?
I'm Yukiko Konagaya. Konayuki for short.
It came up
while we were passing out tissues.
This could be my lucky color. Brown!
Yellow… that's my lucky color.
Whoa, this parfait has both!
It's an auspicious
chocolate banana parfait!
Konayuki, how are you doing,
compared to before?
Actually, I found a job.
I'm working part-time until it starts.
Really?
She beat you to it, Emma.
I want to earn a proper wage
so that I can gain custody
of my child someday.
Currently, my in-laws are watching them.
I see.
I want to play with my child at a park
where there are no moms
trying to outcompete one another.
I want my child to grow up to be
a kind person who doesn't judge others.
"Influencer,"
"wife," "mother"…
It feels like a burden has been lifted
now that I'm none of these things.
But… it's a bit lonely
to come home to an empty apartment.
But this is who I am right now.
This is me, without a filter.
Then…
How about,
you come to this café
whenever you feel lonely?
What?
This off-menu parfait costs 480 yen.
Why not stop by sometime?
Otherwise,
it's mostly elderly regulars here.
Thank you very much.
But it's hard to come
to a café full of regulars.
The elderly customers
primarily visit before noon and afternoon.
This place is empty
during lunchtime and evenings.
I get it. Café regulars
can be a bit too friendly.
Sometimes, you want to be
by yourself but not alone.
Like, you're not completely forgotten,
but you're also not talking to anyone.
Emma, what if you work here
and discourage the other customers
from approaching her?
You're getting ahead of yourself.
This isn't your café.
Actually, she owns this café.
Come again?
She hired me to run the place.
What? Really?
What if you work here on weekdays
and be my assistant
for my fortune-telling on weekends?
Then you can save up,
find a place, and move out.
Of course, you may wait
for your government aid to be approved.
No. I'd love to work here.
Thank you so much!
It worked out for you.
Oh, Konayuki.
This is all thanks to my lucky color.
The fried piroshki from the other day,
this parfait…
Lucky color…
A good encounter, huh.
Let's both do our best.
Yes.
I might stop by if you're working here.
By all means!
Your action determines
your future, correct?
Emma,
I hope you learn
the egg sandwich recipe, at least.
Yes. I'll give it my all.
Yum!
THIS IS A WORK OF FICTION